{              
    "questions": [
        {
            "question" : "It is a small data sent by a server to a user’s web browser to tell if two request is sent form the same browser.",
            "choices" : [
                "HTTP Cookies",
                "HTTP Request Data",
                "Bit Data"
            ],
            "answer" : "a1"
        },
        {
            "question" : "It is used for session management.",
            "choices" : [
                "HTTP Cookies",
                "HTTP Request Data",
                "Bit Data"
            ],
            "answer" : "b1"
        },
        {
            "question" : "It is stored in browser memory and expire once the browser is closed.",
            "choices" : [
                "HTTP Cookies",
                "HTTP Request Data",
                "Bit Data"
            ],
            "answer" : "c1"
        },
        {
            "question" : "It is a java servlet used to handle HTTP requests and generate responses for a website.",
            "choices" : [
                "HttpServlet",
                "JavaServlet",
                "HttpsServlet"
            ],
            "answer" : "d1"
        },
        {
            "question" : "It is an interface that provides request information for HTTP servlets.",
            "choices" : [
                "HttpServletRequest",
                "HttpServletResponse"
            ],
            "answer" : "e1"
        },
        {
            "question" : "It is an interface that provides Http-specific functionality for sending responses.",
            "choices" : [
                "HttpServletRequest",
                "HttpServletResponse"
            ],
            "answer" : "f1"
        },
        {
            "question" : "It is an interface that contains all the set of methods that a servlet uses to communicate with its servlet container.",
            "choices" : [
                "ServletContext",
                "ServletLibraries"
            ],
            "answer" : "g1"
        },
        {
            "question" : "It gets configuration information from the web.xml file.",
            "choices" : [
                "ServletContext",
                "ServletGet();"
            ],
            "answer" : "h1"
        },
        {
            "question" : "Set, get, or remove attributes from the web.xml file, and provide inter-application communication.",
            "choices" : [
                "ServletContext",
                "ServletSet();"
            ],
            "answer" : "i1"
        },
        {
            "question" : "It is a method of ServletContext Interface that returns the names of the context’s initialization parameters.",
            "choices" : [
                "getInitParameterNames()",
                "getInitParameter()"
            ],
            "answer" : "j1"
        },
        {
            "question" : "It is a method of ServletContext Interface that removes the attribute with the given name from the servlet context.",
            "choices" : [
                "removeAttribute(String name)",
                "deleteAttribute(String name)"
            ],
            "answer" : "k1"
        },
        {
            "question" : "It is responsible for creating the scripts on a web server that handles the responses made for a client’s request to the website.",
            "choices" : [
                "Server-side Scripting ",
                "Client-side Scripting"
            ],
            "answer" : "l1"
        },
        {
            "question" : "Java objects that are intended to play the role of server components in client-server communications.",
            "choices" : [
                "Java Servlets",
                "Java server"
            ],
            "answer" : "n1"
        },
        {
            "question" : "This refers to the process that includes the creation of a servlet up to its destruction.",
            "choices" : [
                "Servlet Life Cycle ",
                "Server Life Cycle"
            ],
            "answer" : "o1"
        },
        {
            "question" : "It is similar to JavaScript that allows a web developer, to embed some programs into the HTML code of a web page.",
            "choices" : [
                "PHP",
                "HTML",
                "CSS"
            ],
            "answer" : "p1"
        },
        {
            "question" : "It is used for web development but is also used as a general-purpose programming language.",
            "choices" : [
                "PHP",
                "HTML",
                "CSS"
            ],
            "answer" : "q1"
        },
        {
            "question" : "It is an asynchronous event driven server-side Javascript runtime environment.",
            "choices" : [
                "Node.js",
                "ASP.net"
            ],
            "answer" : "r1"
        },
        {
            "question" : "A component of Node.js that are imported for use in source code for easier and faster coding.",
            "choices" : [
                "Modules",
                "Server",
                "Request and Response Mechanism"
            ],
            "answer" : "s1"
        },
        {
            "question" : "A component of Node.js that listens to the requests that clients make.",
            "choices" : [
                "Server",
                "Request and Response Mechanism",
                "Modules"
            ],
            "answer" : "t1"
        },
        {
            "question" : "What is the right way of implementing a module?",
            "choices" : [
                "const module = require(‘<Module Name>’)",
                "const module = include('<Module Name>')"
            ],
            "answer" : "u1"
        }
    ]
}